(Leonard:)There's chapters
about potty training,
(Leonard:)and bed-wetting and...
(Leonard:)Masturbation.
(Leonard:)Basically, if something came
out of me, she wrote about it!
(Leonard:)You know what?
Do whatever you want,
(Leonard:)just don't talk to me about it.
(Penny:)Not even the chapter
on the breast-feeding crisis?
(Leonard:)It was not a crisis.
Apparently, I favored the left one.
She got a little lopsided.
Oh, my God, you still go left!
(Raj:)Which celebrity would you say
I look like the most?
(Howard:)Halle Berry.
(Penny:)Why?
(Raj:)Stuart and I are putting
dating profiles online,
(Raj:)and it's one of the questions.
(Raj:)And thank you. I'd kill
for that woman's bone structure.